Add a piece of fabric and use it to make the lower skirt, and hide all the plackets.
In order to make the skirt, we need to measure the upper chest first.
Select the basic original measurement and click three times on the model according to the needed measurement position.
Create a rectangular sheet according to the measurement value.
After creating the sheet, use the Edit virtual model measurement tool to delete the measurement on the model.
After creating the sheet, show the arrangement point, click the sheet, and then click the arrangement point in front of the model.
Adjust the shoulder to make the sheet closer to the model.
When the sheet is arranged,
click the sheet again and use the alignment tool to adjust the position again.
Show all the sheets and confirm that no sheet is inserted, then freeze the top one.
Freeze the top one is to keep the top one in the simulation process, but will not participate in the calculation.
In order to prevent further insertion, reduce the particle diameter of the belt of the skirt first, increase the layer, and reduce the conflict thickness.
And then put the back and center together.
After beginning the simulation, the long-necked belt is placed in the top vest bowl.
After the previous freezing top vest is cut, begin the simulation.
After opening the simulation, the tree bag will be limited to the costume.
After the simulation, continue to freeze the top, so as to prevent the costume from changing later, and the frozen version is still in contact with other versions.
Drag the tree bag to the side of the tree bag, because later it needs to create a bag on the side.
Then select the two sides of the line, according to the line created by the curve, and use it to equalize the board.
To facilitate the subsequent production, the two boards are set as symmetrical boards.
After the board is symmetrical, in addition to the shape of the symmetry, the foam line will also automatically symmetrical.
Then select the two sides of the line, according to the curve, and use it to equalize the board.
After the adjustment is complete, after the simulation is stable, please return the layer to 0, to prevent unnecessary layer recognition.
Then use the rectangle tool to draw a tree bag.
Also create a two times
then create a spirit board.
In the process, you can add the human body curve line and place the board.
After placing, use the line sewing tool to sew the tree belt and board together.
Because the sewing line will have a mutual effect, if you don't move the tree belt, it will be pulled by the skirt board.
After the board is simulated and stabilized, sew the sides together.
Then move the tree belt and simulate it together.
If you simulate it directly, the tree belt will be pulled down by the weight of the skirt board.
In order to prevent it from sliding down, we need to change a fabric for the tree belt.
Choose a new fabric for the tree belt.
Change the fabric to Trim Fusible Rigid.
The Trim Fusible Rigid is a fabric that is not easy to deform.
Trim Fusible Rigid is a fabric that is not easy to stretch.
Trim Fusible Rigid is a fabric that is not easy to bend.
If you simulate it, you will see that the fabric is not very obvious when it is sliding down.
In order to prevent the fabric from sliding down, we will increase the friction coefficient of the fabric.
If you want to make it not slide down, you can use the Trim Fusible Rigid tool again.
Press the tree belt and then press the top 1.
Then I will simulate it again.
Now the tree belt will not slide down.
Then untie all the strips and simulate it.
Let the tree belt and top 1 simulate it again.
The clothing looks damaged.
This is because when the fabric is very close to the human body, the particle diameter is relatively large.
The net may be penetrated.
So it is also possible to decrease the particle diameter of all the strips to 8.
Try to manipulate the pattern again.
Then the clothing will become more stable.
Now the fabric of the table is a fine cotton fabric.
Change the panel fabric to the snow-covered fabric.
Since the snow-covered fabric has a very low density,
it can go back to its original position.
To make the fabric more solid, increase the density to 4.
Open the model again and change the application.
To make other details, increase the density to 15.
Since the panel fabric is larger,
it may be slower to run the computer.
The skirt is a bit short.
Select the bottom and stretch the skirt.
Since there is a bump on the ground,
the skirt will be rolled out of the ground.
If there is a bump on the ground,
Press the button to print out the skirt.
If it's a bit hard to organize,
print out the skirt.
After printing,
the skirt will be opened and then printed out.
Then the skirt will go back to its original position.
You can manually turn the skirt around.
Thank you.